<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1252" standalone="no"?>
<operatorHelp lang="en_EN">
    <!--  This is an example how to specify the translation of operator keys to names. -->

<!--    <operator>-->
<!--      <key>mmdf_operator</key>-->
<!--      <name>MMDF Operator</name>-->
<!--    </operator>-->

    <operator>
        <key>mmdf_source_operator</key>
        <name>MMDF SOURCE Operator</name>
        <synopsis> This operator generates configuration to convert an existing kafka topic into a new k-streams topic,
            Enables user to define which fields correspond to longitude,latitude,identifier and timestamp.
            This information will be later be used during fusion execution to efficiently match records of different
            modalities based on spatial indices, temporal windows and identities provided.
        </synopsis>
    </operator>

    <operator>
        <key>mmdf_transformer_operator</key>
        <name>MMDF TRANSFORMER Operator</name>
        <synopsis> This operator extends configuration to transform,filter,format,repeat (spatial) existing kstreams into a new one .
            Different types of transformations are supported.
        </synopsis>

    </operator>

    <operator>
        <key>mmdf_join_operator</key>
        <name>MMDF JOIN Operator</name>
        <synopsis> This operator appends configuration for a join operation.
            The right and the left kstream configurations can be either a source kstream or a transformed one.
            Different types of join are supported.
        </synopsis>
    </operator>

    <operator>
        <key>mmdf_concat_operator</key>
        <name>MMDF CONCAT Operator</name>
        <synopsis>This operator concatenates two json configuration into a single one.
        </synopsis>
    </operator>

    <operator>
        <key>mmdf_fusion_operator</key>
        <name>MMDF FUSION Operator</name>
        <synopsis>This operator expects a json configuration file generated by other mmdf operators.
            Then it converts it into a kstreams topology and executes the in the process background.
        </synopsis>
    </operator>

    <operator>
        <key>mmdf_shape_file_loader_operator</key>
        <name>MMDF SHAPEFILE Injector</name>
        <synopsis>This operator expects a shapefile configuration containing a single polygon. It reads its boundaries and splits its area into h3 cells.</synopsis>
    </operator>
    <operator>
        <key>mmdf_url_loader_operatorr</key>
        <name>MMDF URL Injector</name>
        <synopsis>This operator uses a url and a polygon area defined in well known text and an h3 target resolution. It ingests for all cells in the area a record of the url.</synopsis>
    </operator>
    <!-- This is how group keys are translated: -->

    <group>
      <key>crexdata</key>
      <name>CREXDATA</name>
    </group>


</operatorHelp>
